A Guide to the University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Annual Reports of the Dean, 1922-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
University of Virginia Division of Continuing Education, Annual Reports of the Dean 1922-1973
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-16/1/4.771
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer from the Division of Continuing Education, 1977 July 11.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of annual reports of the Dean of the Division of Continuing Education and includes statistical and budget information.
In addition, the collection contains statistical reports and budgets. Of interest is an article by Albert G. A. Balz Teaching by Mail and the American University.
Arrangement
The reports are arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1922-1924 (Folder 1)
- Statistics- Extension, 1922-1925 (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1923-1926, 3 folders (Folder 1)
- Statistical Report- Extension Activities, 1925-1926 (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1926-1927 (Folder 1)
- Statistical Report- Extension Activities, 1926-1927 (Folder 1)
- Extension Activities, 1926-1959 (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1927-1928 (Folder 1)
- Statistical Report- Extension Activities, 1927-1928 (Folder 1)
- Budget- Extension, 1928-1930, 2 folders. (Folder 1)
- Extension Activities, 1929-1930 (Folder 1)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1929-1953 (Folder 1)
- Annual Reports, 1930-1931 (Folder 2)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1930-1931 (Folder 2)
- Budget- Extension, 1930-1931 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1931-1932 (Folder 2)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1931-1932 (Folder 2)
- Budget- Extension, 1931-1932 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1932-1934, 2 folders. (Folder 2)
- Newcomb, J. H.- Correspondence re Annual Budget, 1933-1935 (Folder 2)
- "Teaching by Mail and the American University"- Dr. Balz's Report, 1934 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1934-1935 (Folder 2)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1934-1935 (Folder 2)
- Academic Faculty, 1934-1956 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1935-1937, 2 folders. (Folder 2)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1936-1937 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1937-1938 (Folder 2)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1937-1938 (Folder 2)
- Annual Report, 1938-1939 (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1938-1939 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1940-1943, 3 folders. (Folder 3)
- Resume of Extension Work at the University of Virginia, 1943 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1943-1944 (Folder 3)
- Budget- Extension, 1943-1944 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1944-1945 (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1944-1945 (Folder 3)
- Budget- Extension, 1944-1945 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1945-1946 (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1945-1946 (Folder 3)
- Budget- Extension, 1945-1946 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1946-1947 (Folder 3)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1946-1947 (Folder 3)
- Budget- Extension, 1946-1947 (Folder 3)
- Annual Report, 1947-1948 (Folder 4)
- Budget- Extension, 1947-1948 (Folder 4)
- Department Reports, 1947-1948 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
- Annual Reports- Extesnion Activities, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
- Budget- Extension, 1948-1949, 2 folders. (Folder 4)
- Budget Request, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
- Budget- Department Requests, 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
- Darden, Jr., Colgate W. (President of UVA), 1948-1949 (Folder 4)
- Budget Estimate, 1948-1950 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1949-1950 (Folder 4)
- Budget- Proposed, 1949-1950 (Folder 4)
- Progress Report- Northern Virginia, 1949-1952 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1950-1951 (Folder 4)
- Annual Reports- Mt. Lake, 1950-1951 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1951-1952 (Folder 4)
- Budget Requests, 1953-1954 (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1952-1954, 2 folders. (Folder 4)
- Annual Report, 1954-1959, 5 folders. (Folder 5)
- Annual Reports- Extension Activities, 1958-1959 (Folder 5)
- Annual Report, 1959-1962, 3 folders. (Folder 5)
- Annual Report, 1962-1967, 5 folders. (Folder 6)
- Annual Report, 1966-1968, 3 folders. (Folder 7)
- Individual Reports, 1967-1968, 2 folders. (Folder 7)
- Annual Report, 1968-1969 (Folder 8)
- Individual Reports, 1968-1969, 2 folders. (Folder 8)
- Annual Report, 1969-1970, 2 folders. (Folder 8)
- Individual Reports, 1969-1970 (Folder 9)
- Programs in Continuing Education, 1970 October (Folder 9)
- Annual Report, 1970-1971, 3 folders. (Folder 9)
- Individual Center Reports and Extension Instruction, 1970-1971 (Folder 9)
- Annual Report (Work Sheets), 1971-1972 (Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1971-1972, 2 folders. (Folder 10)
- Individual Center Reports and Extension Instruction, 1971-1972 (Folder 10)
- Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Folder 10)
- School of General Studies- Conferences and Institutes, n.d. (Folder 10)